A Finding Aid to the Peter Howard Selz papers, 1929-2014, bulk 1950-2005, in the Archives of American Art AAA.selzpete
Archives of American Art
- Scrapbooks, 1947-2012; Series 10; 1.3 Linear feet Box 29-31
  - Binder 2: 1960-1965 (Box 29, Folder 10-12)
  - Binder 3: "Berkeley" 1965-1969 (Box 29, Folder 13-14)
  - "University Art Museum Publicity Selections 1965/1966" Binder (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Binder 4: 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 29, Folder 16-18)
  - Binder 5: 1980s, 1980-1988 (Box 29, Folder 19-20)
  - Binder 5: 1980s, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Binder 6: 1990s, 1990-1999 (Box 30, Folder 2-4)
  - Binder 6: 1990s Miscellaneous, 1990-1999 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    Loose materials including photographs and cards tucked into binder sleeve.
  - Binder 7: 2000-2009, 2000-2007 (Box 30, Folder 6-8)
  - Binder 8: 2006-2012 (Box 31, Folder 1-2)